

Kiệt Nguyễn

Director Of Operations And Business Development at VGI Vietnam

Connect

♠ Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month



Connect

♠ Message

• • •

Kiệt Nguyễn · 3rd

Director Of Operations And Business Development at VGI Vietnam

Vietnam · 500+ connections · Contact info

TransAd Vietnam

Ho Chi Minh city University of law

People and pages related to Kiệt

See all

X

>



Search Engine Journal

Page • Publishing



Follow



Publicis Media

Page • Marketing & Advertising 170,149 followers

Follow



Search Engine Land

Page • Internet 84,836 followers

Follow

About

Skilled in Marketing Management, Business Planning, Advertising, Hotel Management, Business Development, Key Account Management, Legal Advisor, National Representatives.

Activity

3,497 followers



#hiring #experience #project #project #engineer #accounting...

Kiệt shared this 8 Reactions



Happy Tet! Vạn sự như ý!

Kiệt shared this 4 Reactions

Chúc mừng anh!

Kiêt commented



Cần tuyển Project Manager + Engineer (Technical Manager) Fil...

Kiệt shared this

1 Reaction

See all activity

Experience

General Manager

TransAd Vietnam · Full-time
Jan 2021 – Present
· 4 mos
Vietnam

Director Of Operations And Business Development

VGI Vietnam · Contract Oct 2020 – Present · 7 mos Vietnam

Director Of Business Development | Vietnam Market



Managing Director

Newgroup Lmt
Dec 2016 – Apr 2019
· 2 yrs 5 mos
Vietnam

Head of Hospitality

Công Ty Cổ Phần Fiditour

May 2011 – May 2017

6 yrs 1 mo

General Manager

Show 1 more experience 🗸

Education

Ho Chi Minh city University of law

Bachelor's degree, Law 2016 – 2018

2007

Bachelor of Hospitality and Tourism Management- Australia, Hospitality and Tourism 2007-2010

2002

Diploma in Hotel Management- Malaysia, Hospitality 2002 – 2005

Skills & endorsements

Hospitality . 16

Ewout van Voorst and 15 connections have given endorsements for this skill

Tourism . 12

Ewout van Voorst and 11 connections have given endorsements for this skill

Event Management . 9

Tony Ton and 8 connections have given endorsements for this skill

Industry Knowledge

```
Marketing Strategy . q
Hospitality Management . 5
Strategic Planning . 4
Online Marketing . 3
Marketing Management . 2
Business Planning . 3
Event Planning . 2
Pre-opening . 2
Advertising . 1
Market Research . 1
Project Planning . 1
Hotel Management . 1
Research
Business Development . 1
Account Management
Business Management
Sales Operations
Hotels . 9
Interpersonal Skills
Teamwork . 4
```

Contract Negotiation . 2

Negotiation
Management
Languages
English . 1
Other Skills 👩
Hospitality Industry . 7
Marketing Communications . 3
Resorts . 1
Presentation Development . 1
Promotions
Show less ^

Recommendations

Received (1) Given (0)

Irvine Loo

Director of Digital Marketing at Berjaya Hotels & Resorts

October 8, 2020, Irvine was senior to Kiệt but didn't manage directly

Very passionate to hospitality industry and willing to put extra efforts in discover opportunities despite beyond scope of expertise. Most importantly being able to maintain high integrity in challenging work environment is what made him unique.

Language

English

Interests

The Recruitment Network



The Reconstitute of Network 532,910 members

PwC



3,452,403 followers

GE



4,155,216 followers



Arne Sorenson in



President and CEO at Marriott International

314,591 followers

Satya Nadella 🛅



CEO at Microsoft 3,920,299 followers

Digital Marketing: Social Media, Search, Mobile & more

Digital 742,566 members
Marketing

See all

People also viewed



Thuy Nguyen •2nd

Co-Founder at Leaders Create Leaders

Connect



Hoai Phung Nguyen •3rd

Just Do It

Connect



My Hoang Tran •2nd

Head of Sales and Business Development at PIXXOR Vietnam (Thailand)

Connect



Duc Nguyen •3rd

Open for Business Development and Operating job // English bilingual

Connect



Grace Tong •3rd Founder at XÙXÌ Design

Connect

Show more Show more

People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Connect



Nhi Duong

Connect

∨Show more



Add new skills with these courses



10,572 viewers



5,039 viewers



40,678 viewers

Show more on LinkedIn Learning



About

Accessibility

Talent Solutions

Community Guidelines

Careers	
Marketing Solutions	
Privacy & Terms ✓	
Ad Choices	
Advertising	
Sales Solutions	
Mobile	
Small Business	
Safety Center	
Questions? Visit our Help Center.	
Manage your account and privacy Go to your Settings.	
Select Language	
(Arabic) العربية	
LinkedIn Corporation © 2021	
	C/

